Contact

nicoleinfm@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nicole-dodge-04879691 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Photography
Photojournalism
Digital Photography

Nicole Dodge

Junior Web Developer / Professional Wedding Photographer Dallas

Summary

Experinced freelance Photograoher with areas of expertise in Weddings & Elopements, Sports, Concerts/Festival and Graduation/ Seniors. Also have been featured in travel blogs and contracted on branding work for social media accounts.

6+ Years of experience with customer service through serving and bartending as well as lifeguarding at a hotel & resort. Some sales experience as well. (B2C & B2B)

Experience

Nikki Dodge Photography Wedding Photographer January 2018 - Present (3 years 10 months) Remote

Wedding & Elopements

AfterDark Entertainment
Photographer
January 2019 - February 2021 (2 years 2 months)

Gristmill River Restaurant and Bar Server / Expo April 2018 - February 2021 (2 years 11 months)

Disco Donnie Presents
Performer Liaison
April 2019 - April 2020 (1 year 1 month)
UBBI DUBBI Music Festival

Staffing coordinator assistant / performer liaison

Texas State University
Team Photographer
August 2018 - March 2020 (1 year 8 months)
San Marcos, Texas, United States

In charge of the photography for all live football events, sideline coverage and social media content.

Paylidify
Executive Account Manager
October 2017 - March 2019 (1 year 6 months)

AfterDark Entertainment
Event Promoter
January 2018 - January 2018 (1 month)
The marc

Education

The University of Texas at Austin – Center for Professional Education (CPE)

Coding Bootcamp · (2021 - 2021)

Texas State University

Bachelor of Arts - BA, International Relations and Affairs · (2016 - 2020)